

Ye Kyaw Tun *Mechanical Engineer*

Contact

Address: Yangon, Myanmar.

Phone: +95 9400015146

E-mail: uyekyawtun@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://ye-kyaw-tun.github.io/2023

Skills

English, Japanese
Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
AutoCAD (2D, 3D, ISO)
Site Supervision

Education

Bachelor of Mechanical Engineering

[15-Feb-2015]

Government Technological University

Personal Information

Father's Name: U Tun Myint Date of birth: 21st, July 1993 Marital Status: Married

NRC No: 1/HaPaNa (N) 003385

Religion: Buddhist

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic Mechanical Engineer with over 3 years of experience in plant commissioning with Japanese Engineers at Thilawa-SEZ. HSE Manager with over 1 year of experience in Garment Factory. SHEQ Officer with 2 year of experience in Paint Production Factory. Sales Engineer with 2 years of experience in safety equipment distribution and training Company.

Work Experiences

Mechanical Engineer

[Feb.2021-Present]

J-SAT General Services Co., Ltd. (KEC Myanmar)

- Work closely with supplier teams to ensure that all systems, equipment, and components are installed correctly and meet design specifications.
- Coordinate and oversee the execution of various testing activities, including operation tests, performance tests, and safety tests, to ensure systems operate efficiently and safely.
- Provide training to plant operators and maintenance teams on newly commissioned systems and equipment to ensure proper operation and upkeep.

HSE Manager

[Jan.2019 - May.2020]

Myanmar I-Tex Garment Co., Ltd.

- Responsible for ensuring that the company understands and complies with all laws and regulations regarding health, safety, and the environment.
- Responsible for health and safety requirements for all inspections such as Government inspector, <u>BSCI</u>, <u>WRAP</u>, <u>OEKO-TEX</u>, etc...
- Report all incidents immediately to management, investigate all incidents fully, and advise management on how to prevent similar incidents in the future.

SHEQ Officer

[Jan.2017 - Nov.2018]

UPG - Paints & Coating Co., Ltd.

- Inspect Safety Instructions and Rules Compliance regarding (Employee Safety, Process Safety, Environment Safety, Distribution Safety) and supervise the employees to comply.
- Periodic arrangements with the township Health Department for the employee's medical checkup.
- Implementation of the Occupational Health and Safety Management System (OHSAS 18001) and Environmental Management System (ISO 14001) requirements according to the guidelines and procedures.
- Supervising Hazardous and Non-hazardous waste disposal.
- Inspects the performance of pest control services monthly.

Sales Engineer

[Feb.2015 - Jul.2016]

Win OSHE Services Co., Ltd

- Provide technical documentation, including product specifications, manuals, and guides, to support clients' understanding and usage of products.
- Inspects Delivery of goods to customers, and made regular follow-ups for usage and feedback.